whatcms.org 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy - What CMS?

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from WhatCMS.org (the “Site”).

## PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, and date/time stamps.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, payment information , email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
  * We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site.

## SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our sharing of your personal data is very limited and a requirement for us to operate our Site.

If you sign up for an api plan, your personal details will be processed by Stripe. Stripe's privacy policy is available here: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

All http requests to our Site are routed through Cloudflare's CDN. Cloudflare's privacy policy is available here: <https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/>

We display advertising on our Site with the help from Google Adsense and BuySellAds. Google's privacy policy is available here: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>. BuySellAds privacy policy is available here: <https://www.buysellads.com/about/privacy>.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

## BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

## DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

## YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

## DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

## CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

## CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at admin@mg.whatcms.org.
